(Exhales) (Bell Dings)
our
.</
I gave a short of everyone.
You already have met
Swati, Sanjia and Hanuk.
Hari is from our production team and
Swati is more from the
post-production team.
So Hari right now edited your demo screen
share that you shared.
And then we shared it with Sanjia and
Hanuk for the final review.
So then Hanuk has a few
observations on the screen share.
The way you are creating is still okay
but the concept on which it's been...
created is not being understandable as
per my understanding of Hanuk.
So I'll hand it over to Hanuk.
Hanuk can explain better
as to what is the issue.
And before that, Hari, can you play that
video for us to understand that the audio
and video are not syncing.
So in one of the slides, as per Hari,
slide 6 audio is coming in slide 7 audio,
something like that.
All right, very good.
Let's try it and see it and try to
understand it because what I did was, if
I share my screen, before we start, I
created a video around this as well.
So you guys should be able to see this.
Can you guys see my screen?
Yes.
So what I tried to do was I tried to edit
it myself so I will be able to see it
myself as well, put myself into the same
shoes with the post-production team.
So what I did was, in
a nutshell, on here,
first of all, what I did was I gave you
guys Google Drive folders for
everything, for the voiceover.
So the voiceover can
be changed at any place.
It is at the bottom.
There is a voiceover.
So the voiceover can be
easily tracked everywhere.
So how can it be tracked the voiceover?
If you guys see the file names, there is
a voiceover file name.
And that voiceover file
name is on Storyboard.
But do not use the
Storyboard to line up the audio.
The audio is in the voiceover audio file.
But how are you going to put the
voiceover audio to the correct slide?
That key lands in the slide.
So all of this combo has at
the bottom a voiceover posted.
So once you look at the voiceover post-
You know that how it's going to land
because I put these voiceovers.
I did not edit them.
I put a Rough voiceover so it will be one
second behind one second after so they
had to be mapped with these voiceovers at
the bottom post-its and I put all these
Screen captures with the number coding on
here So in the combat you should be able
to find it with the number codes and the
number codes are already placed In the
output slides so they are very
straightforward and I put all the
references into one file and created this
into a Video format that could be easily
found if this says scene 5 that it is the
fifth scene In the system, and how do you
place it on timeline?
I put the storyboard as you guys will be
able to listen it and do it easily And
all of these scenes have seen numbers
Inside them so you know which scene you
are at without even looking at combo But
combo is there to be able to support you
I put this into the wind result You will
be able to see the scene
number as for s5 s6 as we
Start off the scene.
This is the rough audio as you guys see
scene is here But there's one second gap
you need to move this to the left hand
side There is one second gap you need to
move this to the left hand side.
I did not cut this I expected the
post-production team to cut it and place
it, but don't forget.
There's also the Posted notes which has
the voiceovers on top of tanda so that in
the editing It should be able to go there
And you are not going to use the
voiceover on the storyboard You are going
to use the voiceover in the module one to
be able to place it properly So there's a
clean voiceover as well
that I recorded in audiosity
you place the footage
for the screen capture.
You know the footage ID and
you know the scene over there.
You are going to meet the storyboard,
place it in the correct place and set the
screen capture over there.
Then you are going to collect the visuals
and do a sanity check because I put the
visuals onto the combo by going into
combo and being able to download it by
right clicking on it and do a download
selection on here in a very easy manner.
So that's going to
help you be able to do it
directly over here.
So there's a voiceover
screen capture over there.
So that will let you be
able to download it as well.
So that is in a nutshell.
Which part is the problematic part for
you, Hanukkah, in here
to be able to not do it?
I'll tell you, see the thing is,
now like once this gets edited, once the
audio is in sync, maybe I might have a
different opinion, but see the thing is
still the problems which I foresee is
whatever you were
mentioning in the narration, right?
And whatever is there in the screen, like
I understand that those things are
relatable because we
have additional information,
not excess information on the screen, but
the narration is talking about some
generic things and it's much more
abstract, not kind of specific.
This is what I felt.
And as I've already said that the
voiceover and demo is,
just a second, let me
complete, maybe you can add after that.
Otherwise I'll lose my train of thought
if that's okay with you.
So as I was saying, the
voiceover and the demo was not.
modern sync, first of all.
So you said that maybe we might have to
adjust it a little bit, then that
particular thing would be solved.
But still, as I've said, the second
problem was that there were a lot of
things on the screen, but I can
understand that from a technical point of
view, maybe as a subject matter expert,
you might find that this is something
which is kind of, these
would be relatable things.
But from a learner's perspective, or when
I look at it things, I cannot relate with
what you are saying.
There are a few things that are there on
the screen, which I can see and what you
are saying, but those
are not in a direct way.
All right, and the
demos, which I see, right?
So the demos also like what I expect is
that the demo should be
for a concrete example.
All right, so and then for a given
concrete example, you would have to kind
of divide the demo into different steps,
like step one, step two, step three.
All right, and then maybe in step one,
you would say that, okay, install this.
All right, maybe there was a step wherein
you go on to GitHub and then over there,
you would have, instead of doing it
locally, you are adding some code spaces,
you are doing it on code spaces.
I do not know, I'm not a technical person
over here to comment on that.
So maybe, so the thing is
you can just take an example,
you can do the demo for an example
scenario, hypothetical scenario or a
hypothetical example, the different steps
involved, and alternatively, you can
mention the different alternative steps,
like you can do this locally as well, but
the focus should be on the example
scenario that you have
taken to meet the objective.
And accordingly, the steps
would have to be broken down.
I'm not expecting you to show the entire
execution of those steps.
You just mentioned the important pointers
or the codes or the steps that the
learner would have to perform
for a given major step, right?
like the first step would be maybe for
installing something.
All right, and then that is where you
show the code for installing, okay, and
this is, I'm just
randomly speaking over here.
I'm not sure if this applies to your demo
or not, but there was a step for
installing installation.
I've seen that.
So you need not to show the entire
process of installation.
You just say that use this code for
installing and then you just skip to that
part where the installation is complete
and then you move on to the next step.
Maybe next step would be kind of maybe
integrating onto the GitHub or doing it
on code spaces or locally.
I'm not sure.
All right, so I want, so at present, it
is very difficult to
understand the flow of the demo.
You know, like what are the steps that
the learner would have to kind of perform
to attain the
objective of the video, right?
Maybe if we are trying to build something
over here, so that building should,
building that particular thing should
involve one, two, three steps, all right?
These steps which would be, which can be
applied for any such example, all right?
Any such example.
So you would have to
take a concrete example.
You would have, your focus should be that
and maybe alternatively, you can mention
few things that can be covered.
So what I felt was this was, there were
portions in the screen shares which felt
more like conceptual portions, all right?
Because there were
generic discussions going on.
You are talking about
generic things, all right?
So those things would have
to be covered in a conceptual,
because okay, these are the
techniques that are involved.
That's fine.
You need not to dig deep into it.
You can tell that, okay, these are the
alternatives that we have.
So that's fine.
And yeah, so this is how I want you to
approach the demo because it's very
difficult to follow at
this particular point.
You can go ahead and add your points.
You talked about only two points.
I'm recording this and I will go over it
to make sure that I understood.
First, you said you are
unable to put the voiceovers.
This is the first part.
The second part you said
you had a flow problem.
Is that correct?
Two points?
Only two.
Let's address the
first one, the voiceovers.
So the voiceovers is
impossible for you not to find.
Impossible.
Because what I'm doing is I put the
voiceovers onto post-its.
And I read the post-its, A1, it starts
here and goes to a transition line.
It says, now let's look at our targets.
If you are able to follow the Kamba,
either on Kamba.com or on the storyboard
video that I gave you, by scene number,
then you will be able to find it.
So the thing is, the post-production team
has S5, S6, all of
them next to each other.
I tried to find it.
I find it.
I'm able to because I read these things
and I put the audio under them, but not
one-to-one, but very,
very close to each other.
There is a cut, there is a start.
They are not 100%, but there
is a cut, there is a start.
So if I take it here and if I play it, I
will be able to hear attack, we apply
perturbation, we
aren't changing the image.
If I hit, I will play, I will hear
visuals, adversarial
samples, they are looking similar.
I'm not going to talk like yourself.
I will talk about one
topic, then go to the other one.
Please answer what is the issue here.
How do you can get?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So this one, I got it that one.
So we can understand it.
So we can fix this one as you are giving
the audio in that story about itself.
So right now we have the problem is if
you go to slide five, so the audio it is
coming up to slide six, it is coming.
Yeah, then cut it.
Just go to.
Then cut it.
Yeah.
I gave it to you.
Cut it then.
I understand this talks on limitations on
here and this talks on the environment.
This is not a simple cut, but cut it.
I put them over here.
So when I say the environment, we have to
decide you are going to see the images
here and you are going to see
the video and I can try you.
Yeah.
After the slide five, we can make a cut
and we can move the remaining part and
from slide six, we can
match the audio part.
So that is fine.
Yes.
So I gave you again, I can I give you
that and I can share that one.
Yes.
I gave you three, four things on here.
First of all, the voiceover is a
screenshot in an image, a video to place
it over and also extra visuals for you to
go ahead, download and
make more sense out of it.
So you will be able to say, okay, Rufat
is talking about this and I
know what he is talking about.
Maybe I should show this image, show this
one or show this video that you will be
able to do either one of them.
So is the point one clear or this is
still too hard for you
guys to map and take?
See no, no, no, see, see, yeah.
I think the audio part, Hari can fix but
my concern is if you go to the slide one,
I'll give you, I'll tell you the example
of what I'm talking about.
When I say things are not in syncy,
whatever you're mentioning in the
narration, right, it clearly does not
discuss everything that is present.
This isn't on the scale.
Okay.
Of course.
Well, here you
mentioned the objectives, right?
Of course.
Just give me a second.
This is a moot board and a storyboard for
you to show what is up, but
I'm reading the posted notes.
I read the posted notes.
Wait, wait.
I read the posted notes explaining what
is here with a transition line.
So there is always a flow.
Which answers your second question?
Okay, just give me a second.
So over here, you're saying in the
narration, you're saying welcome to the
Evasion Attacks Lab.
Today our objectives
is simple but dangerous.
We are going to break a production ready
AI model using
nothing but math and noise.
So this is there in your voiceover.
But over here on screen, I can say KR1
reproducibility, then KR2.
So this is code clarity.
So these things are not mentioned.
This is not mentioned or this is not
talked about in the narration, the
corresponding narration.
So what we are going to do is, I'm
telling you what we are going to do is
show a big picture of your objective is
simple and dangerous.
Break your production ready model using
nothing but math and noise.
So that's my voiceover.
I'm going to go ahead and
do all these objectives.
I'm not taking
everything from this image.
This image is a storyboard.
You can use it, you might not use it.
So this is a storyboard image.
You can use the math and noise.
You can use the Evasion Attack Labs as a
big image that is coming
on here, but not everything.
You do not have to use everything.
This is a storyboard.
All of these images, it includes.
Once I go here, our first
key is the environmental.
We will deploy a fully reproducible.
Attackers Playbook repository for FGSM,
which is the hello world.
It says the hello world.
This is not going to be used.
What I'm doing is I
created the flow first.
My goal, Honuki, the main
goal is creating the flow.
I created objectives first.
Then I created an environment.
So the person has an environment.
Then I created the user interfaces.
Then I created all the formulas, all the
steps that they are going to follow.
Then I created all the
symbols that are used.
They are using AI to install the symbols.
Then I showed them the errors.
Then I showed them how
they are going to test it.
So there is two flows.
There is one flow inside the narration.
There is the second flow
going through the one slide.
There is the other slide
and there is an overall flow.
Yeah, that is understood.
My concern is only...
That are already
being designed and placed.
See, I understand.
See, there are transitions
from one slide to the other slide.
That is completely there.
I'm not denying that fact.
My concern is like I already said, you
have provided some images.
So the video which I have received is the
final produced video is the video that
contains all these images
along with the voiceover.
And if we include all the information
that you provided in the slides...
Not all the information.
No, no, no, no, no.
I said you guys are going to
do editing post-production.
Not all of the information.
You are not going to
include this title all the time.
include this image all the time.
You are not going to include this
post-node scene number as an editor.
But I can edit it with the
footage that I have provided.
You are going to listen.
You are going to see and then edit
something and create another...
storyline which lines up with audience
such as in here what I say for example
macOS users you are going to show them
MacBook and one M2 chips you are going to
show and one M2 chips often facing
TensorFlow capability you are going to
show TensorFlow I am showing the download
on here might not have the visual studio
code this part is the visual studio code
if you want I can also give those images
on here but I understand that you guys
find this am I correct that's the
challenge basically Rifat that yeah so
basically as in like you are the subject
matter expert the way you know the
content like it we won't be able to
exactly pick up which ones which parts to
use and which parts to not use like will
it be very difficult for you to provide
us the demo because that way we will we
will be able to meet Korsera's
expectation to to use demonstration
instead of images and your work and our
work also I didn't only put images hold
on hold on we are mixing I also put the
videos and I gave you 10 different videos
on here with all the hand zones I gave
you guys the screen captures and the
videos the audience knows what they are
going to do you guys have images sound
videos and the flow on post-production go
ahead sir we are facing the problem here
so if we sound in some slides you have
included images and the videos also so
when it comes to for this audio first we
have to show the image or first we have
to show the video photos so that editors
are facing the that issue so from exactly
we have to show which one anyway first we
have to show the video or
first we have to show the image
This was that doubt we are having.
So do you guys want me to write to you
guys a post-production plan on here, how
you guys are going to edit it?
No, no, that'll even, that'll add one
more layer to, one more layer to the
already, there are too many layers right
now at this screen share.
The best and the easiest and the most
effective way would be, guys, please tell
me if I'm wrong, if you
record the demo for us.
I recorded the demo.
Exactly, of course I love the models.
These are the recorded demos.
These are the recorded demos I gave.
Okay, the first.
Tense screen capture videos and put them
onto the mood board.
But for us to be able to reach here, I'm
talking beforehand, before
this slide, it says environment.
Let's talk about the
environment to run these attacks.
We need a setup that supports a Python
library, such as TensorFlow image
processing without crashing your laptop.
But here is your constraint.
I'm talking about this, showing them the
TensorFlow install, then taking them to
here, local setups, open face, hell-rung
Python versions, missing libraries.
I'm showing them the GitHub code space.
Yeah, yeah, I referred, I'm asking so far
this slide five, if we have to, for this
audio, we have to
show only the video part.
No, video and image.
You have two images also.
No, no, video and image.
So that also we have to show.
We have to show the image.
But is it so that when you are-- Only we
are having the issue.
So where exactly where we have to show
the image and where we
have to show the video.
So that confusion we are having.
If you guys want, I already gave you guys
all the storyboards.
I can also provide the edited version,
post-production version of this video and
show you guys how I edit it.
I can also edit this and
also write the post-production.
Then you can take it and understand,
okay, this is end-to-end where the image
comes in, where the audio comes in.
I can also do that in the
post-production, but I will finish all
the post-production edit.
No, no, actually post-production, our
team can handle, that's not a problem,
but wouldn't it be easier for you to
record the demo than to edit everything?
Swati, I think the issue here is that the
demo is recorded, like those videos that
are embedded are the
hands-on demo, right?
Yes. That are there, that comes in parts.
But there is a part of
voiceover which needs to have
our developed slides, like in the
beginning, like we were talking about Mac
and whatever, then we put up a Mac image
or whatsoever, that part we have to do.
And then for the current slide, there is
a portion of the image that comes first,
then the demo plays, the
image that is attached.
Rifat, am I right on this part?
Yes, but what I'm thinking is right now,
how they are looking at it is without
putting the cognitive part, they just
want to be able to, I also understand,
this is an advanced
course, not an easy course.
So what I can do is, I can use the
footages that I gave you guys, finish one
video's edit, because there is going to
be 10 modules, and show you guys the plan
and how I edited it, and only use the
files that I've given you guys, and also
find MacBook images and do the
placements, and it will be easier for you
guys, which steps I have gone through,
because there is
three stages of the flow.
One flow with the audio, one flow within
all video structure, and one flow with
the artifacts inside the scenes.
I think what you guys are having an issue
is, I did not include the artifacts
inside the scenes flow.
You guys are unable to place them.
Did I understand it correctly?
I gave you guys the title, I gave you
guys the voiceover, I gave you guys the
videos and the images, but I did not give
you guys how it is flowing.
So it is creating a hard time because you
guys are not subject matter experts.
Which one you guys are going to show and
you guys are unable to make the decision
on what to show, what not to show.
Yeah, exactly that is the point.
Now, even if you'll edit one video, when
we come to the next one, how will we
again understand what has to come with?
So the question is how
we as laymen understand.
First of all, once I finish the editing
of this video, I will have two things.
One, editing plan.
The second, an output that
I like that you guys like.
You guys can say, "I like this edit, I
don't like this edit."
But we will also edit the edit plan.
Then you guys will say, "Okay, just give
me the edit plan in the next videos and
we will edit through this."
That edit plan will include artifact by
artifact, meaning this lower third will
come, this image will come, this screen
capture will come, and that output will
be at the output video capture that you
guys will be able to see.
Two outputs, one final video output and
then the planned video output.
So all of them will be in one video.
So, Rifat, then if that is the only
solution, Hano, please correct me if I'm
wrong and Sangya, please
correct me if I'm wrong.
So you don't have to edit exact thing,
just give us a rough
structure because I don't know.
want you to put in a lot of effort
because anyways we are
going to redo it here.
We have professional editors who do it.
So just give us a rough structure in
terms of so that it gives
us clarity what comes where.
I already gave the rough structure.
In a video if you can
give us the rough structure.
I already gave the rough structure.
But since it got very confusing since
they were canvas lights there were a lot
of confusion and mismatch of the audio.
So if that only you
can put it in a video.
No what I will do is.
Please correct me if I'm wrong.
I will edit this on DaVinci Resolve and
record myself while editing it.
So you guys will be
able to see how I edit it.
How I do my selections.
And to end with the plan.
So I will be like the video production
assistant on the editing side.
So it will be easier.
I think if we will see you like somewhere
in the screen on the screen that will be
a little problem because we would want to
have the full HD version of it.
No no I will give two of it.
And then definitely we
will find you that at our end.
I will give one video
output as the edited version.
The second I will give you guys the plan.
The third I will give you guys how I edit
it on DaVinci Resolve.
Is
that all right?
I think Swati is absolutely right.
I think this is causing
too much work for you for us.
And if we calculate the time that we are
taking for the review process itself it's
adding to a lot of time for this course.
So we want to simplify the process rather
than you investing so much time into it.
Because like you said time is money.
Let's do it that way.
So we don't want anybody to invest extra
effort into you know editing then us
viewing it and then going forward to it.
Although that is the
process of learning we'd say.
But as a business model I would say.
that we will have to be a little more
conscious on the time that we're
investing in one video
production of only one screen share.
If the easy way out, if it could be, was
that while, that is my idea of it.
Can you just put, like you put it on the
Canva board, you put every, this thing,
every line of your script and then given
us a video and a photo.
And it's all on one Canva.
So that is what is getting us confused.
I already gave my cover.
So rather than that, can you?
I already gave my cover and voiceover or
post it lost with scene IDs.
And the audio is very
close to the scenes.
So like in one of the, one slide, there
is an audio, there is an image and
there's a voiceover and then there's a
script part of it, right?
Now all of that, where to
put what is the question here?
So to simplify that,
can we have a simple,
breakdown of the sentence that you're
speaking and what image you
want to get in front of it?
Just that much.
All right, you guys want the plan.
With this sentence, you
want this video to come in.
I will create the post production plan.
That post production plan is,
I have done it multiple times.
I will give you guys
the post production plan.
Where image, when the audio comes in, I
will give you guys the
post production plan.
It's not very, very hard because I have
the video, I have the audio.
I will go to chat GPT, create me a post
production plan and put it there so you
guys will be able to use the AI and see
there's a post production plan and the
post production plan will include all the
images, audio that
should be displayed on here.
I can definitely give that, yes.
And it will not take too much of my time.
And I will use the AI to
create the post production.
plan with the existing stuff that we
already have on the scene.
Okay, I just have one.
Yeah, I'll just tell one more thing.
See the thing over here is like if you're
switching in between a lot of images, a
lot of videos in between.
So I see that the
voiceover is not very long.
All right.
The corresponding narration, it's hardly
of two, three lines or so.
Okay, so there is not
enough settlement time.
Just give me a second.
So there is not enough settlement time
for the learner to kind of comprehend of
what comes on the screen.
Like I see there are a
lot of code snippets, right?
So there are a lot of codes involved.
Like if you say that, okay, for visual
studio code, we're
going to show this image.
All right.
So there are a lot of
codes involved in that.
So it would just come and go.
It would not add any learning
value for the learner, right?
So there is not enough time that we are
spending on that image, the different
codes that are written in that.
Like so, like it's very difficult from a
learner's perspective to kind of
understand what is written in that.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
So that is what I meant
when things are not in secret.
Hold on, okay.
Don't forget.
This is, I compressed this video from,
this is right now at six, seven minutes,
once it's all edited
out, the, what's her name?
The mom met once only three minutes.
This is an advanced course because we are
going to create 10 of them.
We are compressing them.
In the future, I will
even compress it further.
There is right now 40 scenes.
In my future ones, I will
only create 10 scenes, not 40.
This is an advanced level course, but we
are trying to fit into 60 minute
timeline, not six hours timeline.
Do you understand what I mean?
Yeah, so that is what, so
I completely understand.
trying to go fast.
If I shoot this in one go,
it will cost it one hour.
Then the mom mate will say
one video capture one hour.
What are you doing?
Do you understand?
Maybe what we can.
Yeah, I understand.
See, like I'll tell you.
So if you go to them up,
don't forget I speeded up these voice
captures, the screen captures.
They are in 3x, 4x.
Don't forget such as once I go to these
videos, if you play them, you are going
to realize these are running very, very
fast and down below.
If we can't hear you, you're on mute.
Once if you look at these screen
captures, these are in 4x, 3x.
These ones are also going very fast.
Let's just take this as an example.
So let's see the voice over corresponding
to this particular screen.
Let's just review this slide.
I'll tell my observations on this.
Okay, you are saying you could start.
What's the voice over?
It's right up on Python 3 and the
connection status and we are live.
Time to run it.
I'm running it in the background and at
the end I'm going to see the Python 3
online that comes on here.
First of all, we asked the AI, artificial
intelligence, for us to run it.
This is the first thing that comes on.
Then there is this video
that shows Python that runs.
This is the start and this is the end.
And okay, so this is of how much time?
This screen share, this
is of how much duration?
Now see this screen share,
this is of how many seconds?
16 seconds, 16.7.
This is of screen.
And see the voice over is not enough.
There is a 16 seconds of
and then like you're saying and and and
it's very like if you could pull up the
voiceover corresponding to this which
which you have written.
See your journalist connected your right
up you will be able to see the Python 3
server ensure your kernel is yes and this
is where we show it.
This is going to be shown at the start we
run this you're saying in the top right
in the top right you should see Python
where can I see it on the top right?
It should be here on the point.
Python running here.
It says running type, right corner.
It's on the left.
So left.
OK, so the voiceover says see so see like
like we're just reviewing one slide.
So this is what so then the voiceover
says like as editors they do not know
where actually the
Python program is running.
So the voiceover says the learner would
be looking for where the Python program
is running because the narration says
that on the type top right corner there
is this Python 3 running
like they would not be.
I'm just saying from a.
Editor's job is to
make sure this is usable.
Yes, I understand that editor's job is
thinking and making the best out of it.
Sometimes I read the same
sentence multiple times.
Editor's job is cut the ones that are not
going to get used and only use the one
that is going to be used.
But these are very technical.
They can understand like
what what is that we want to.
There are multiple things on the We want
to have your expertise.
So we delete the right.
Well, but they won't be able to...
No, no, that is easy or post-production.
What if something is deleted which is
very crucial as per you?
That is easy or post-production.
Delete the right keyword,
only use the top keyword.
It is easy.
You use your mind.
But they are not...
My post-production team is not refered.
They are not away from you.
So they won't be able
to know what to delete.
That is the struggle that we are facing.
I think we need to have you on a call
while we are editing.
You know, like what can we take?
Yes, let's edit together.
Okay.
Hanoi, I will connect to you.
We can edit together.
That's also fine.
I can help you edit.
I do not do editing.
Like I just reviewed the final video.
I just reviewed the final video.
So I'm not part of editing, no?
So I'm not involved in that process.
I get the final video for reviewing.
Okay, one last thing, one more thing.
So there is one more line which you said,
"ensure the kernel is connected," right?
So for that, you're saying
there is a 16 seconds of demo.
Now, where is that process?
Like how would the learner ensure?
But you're actually showing...
So I think the narration
should be in a different way.
Maybe see, this is how you
would have to connect the kernel.
You have that 16 seconds of demo.
Correct me if I'm right or wrong.
Because see, it's very difficult for the
learner to comprehend like how are they
actually connecting the
kernel, how they should ensure it.
Unless and until if you have shown it and
there is a corresponding voiceover to
that, they will not
be able to understand.
So that is what I'm saying.
So I...
So this is good though.
But I will do, if I was your position, I
will create a three second animation and
put a kernel connected message on top and
give it and amplify it.
So they understand that the kernel
connection is very, very important.
Did you hear me?
Yeah, I heard you.
Yes, so that's why
people use the animation.
But we have a limited budget.
We have limited time because we cannot
shoot this for one hour.
It's a screen capture.
That's our constraint.
But we need to have a
structure that creates this.
We need to have screen captures and we
have 10 different
tools that goes in and out.
So we use the post-production magic to be
able to make this work.
That is the whole game.
The whole game is we use the
post-production magic, use the production
data, stitch it together so the learner
can understand this.
I'm not saying the post-production team
is not telling a story line.
They are also telling another story line.
Everybody is telling a story line, but I
understand you are
having a hard time doing this.
I will give you a post-production plan.
I will produce one and I will record my
video production steps.
Then I guess in the post-production plan,
you will have everything.
If you are saying, "Rofat, you gave me
the post-production plan."
You produced it, but it doesn't work out
in a way that I expect.
And it is still not
understandable by the end users.
I will fix it again and we will have a
post-production plan ready for you.
So it is easier for you to edit this.
This is where I am at right now from this
output for this video.
And I wanted to have this call multiple
times at MAMet because I understood that
you guys might have a hard time.
And I want to help you guys out to make
sure we are going to do 10 videos like
this on this advanced level course.
And this course is going to be taken by
the audience of OpenAI.
Invidia the people who write the
artificial intelligence chips and the
large language models these Discourses
for them this course is not for a Python
developer that will come in and write
Python We understand this course is how
they are going to secure those models
this the trillion for the trillion dollar
companies this course is not for the
General audience do you guys understand
this is an advanced level course how they
secure their models?
Is that clear Yeah, exactly highly
technical like one suggestion instead of
doing these two three things you can just
give us a rough structure It could be
even 10 15 minutes long with the screen
shares and your voiceover
And We just we'll fine-tune it visually
we'll add whichever element is required
We'll make the those elements will create
them in after effects or canva or in
Premiere Pro wherever is needed my team
will create a Visually like beautify it
and then like the structure you can give
us are you guys using the AI?
Wasting your time and giving us three
things What I will do is I will go use
the AI to create a post-production plan
Read it fix it and give it to you guys I
will use artificial intelligence to be
able to create the post-production plan
and make it sense and Make sure all the
artifacts that are mentioned there are
inside these video slides
and they are in the outputs
That is what I will do
So there is no gaps because the AI will
create a post-production plan and can't
yeah, absolutely my concern my Son then
again will go back to what if that
doesn't work as well and we again will
come back to the same thing No, no if
there is a plan and if I already
the post-production team cannot run away
because there is the produced video and
there is the plan and there is the
footages, input, system and an output.
Where is the
post-production team gonna run?
There is no way to run.
I use the input, I use the
plan and I create an output.
Ali, we want to start on this
project as soon as possible.
Yeah, very good.
I will create your post-production plan
as soon as possible with the output.
That's alright, I will create it.
So you will give us the rough structure?
No, no, I will give you the final output,
I will give you the plan and the
artifacts and show a video how they are
mapping it and how I produce the output.
So I will create a course to create a
post-production video just for this
course so they can follow up the video
and while the artifacts are there, if I
am able to do it post-production, you
guys should be able to do it as well.
By watching the video, we
are creating video courses.
I will create the video
course to do post-production.
And that will work out, right?
I will give you the input, the artifacts.
I am a little skeptical because if we get
too many files again, then there will be
too much confusion, might as well just
get one file and we will fine tune it and
we will do everything and beautify it and
shorten it and make it as per the script.
But we should have that file.
I think Swati, Rifatib, what Swati is
saying, we can do that, I
think that will be the best.
If we get one file with everything and
then maybe it's 10 minutes long, 15
minutes long, that's fine.
We will trim it down as and when based on
Swati and her team's understanding.
That will be the
easiest way of doing this.
If they gave one file,
they couldn't trim it out.
That's the problem.
No, no, no.
Not in the form of Kamba or Kanva, but in
the form of a file only.
I also gave that as well.
There's a storyboard one with the audio
in it, with everything that is shown.
That's the thing.
It's too many files.
Yes, I will give you one post-production
output, the final
video, with no editors used.
That's all we need, that
all we request from you.
Yes, I will give the post-production
output, the edited
version, the plan and other stuff.
You guys will understand this could be
done by using these footages.
He gave us the plan and all the steps and
then go in the behind and think about it.
This is where I am right now.
Because if I can show that this is doable
with the video production, then it will
be able to say, "Okay, this is doable."
But our main goal is to make sure that
what Honoke is saying is also important.
This is understandable by the learners.
Once I finish one video, full
post-production, we are going to say,
"All right, this can be done.
This is
understandable and this is usable."
I also understand Honoke's points there.
There are some gaps.
I will find those gaps.
I will find those gaps and put them to
the post-production plan.
The post-production plan will include all
those steps as well.
There is no gap.
If we are able to confirm the first
video, if I can do the editing of the
first video with all of it, then we will
be able to go ahead and
do the remaining ones.
This is where I am right now.
I need to do at least one video to make
sure we are at the same place.
Maybe the...
number of the video files is overloading
the team, the instructions,
but let's see if I can do it.
If I'm unable to do it, it is not
acceptable for Hanukkah, for Hari, the
post-production of
Sivati to be able to do this.
But if I can do this post-production, you
guys should be able to do it as well.
And if I record all the process,
okay.
Yes, yes.
So while you're addressing these gaps, so
I just wanted to make a point over here.
So like, for example, when you say as I
was giving this example, like ensure that
the kernel is connected.
Instead of saying that, ensure the kernel
is connected because I've seen that
you've been demonstrating that in that 16
second video, right?
So I would suggest you to provide a narration wherein the folks who are with
you you to provide a narration wherein
you explain the process of ensuring how
the kernel is connected.
Instead of just saying in the narration
that ensure that it's connected, we are
actually telling the learner the process
of connecting the kernel.
If you understand what
I'm trying to say over here.
So the process has to be explained.
The process has to be explained instead
of just saying that, make
sure that this is connected.
So it makes much more relatable for the
learner and he would also be able to, he
or she would be able to understand.
Hanukkah, do you know
how I am doing this course?
I'm really turning on a system to be able
to do an AI model security for open AI
for the people who
generate these AI systems.
I am turning them on this system.
There is a working system and there is a
working code base for them.
This is a code base
that is working for them.
I'm giving them the code.
I'm giving them how
it is running on here.
I'm demonstrating
something that is already.
the adversarial evasion lab.
So they are getting end to
end from the start to the end.
But for me to turn it on, I
go through all these steps.
I take the screenshots first.
The screenshots are there.
The system is working.
Then what I do it is
I put the voiceovers.
I read the voiceovers.
Then there's always the transition lines.
And I make sure that I glued the image to
the audio to make sure
that while I'm reading it.
But right now, your problem
is you are unable to see it.
So what I will do it is I will add a
post-production plan so
you will be able to get it.
There is one more person in the call.
I hope we are not going to
explain it one more time.
But I will try to do my best.
Hello, Luma.
How are you?
What we are trying to do is-- Oh, hi.
I found you.
I shared the-- It's twice the head of
the-- I shared the post-production plan
for this screen capture piece for the
module one and video one.
And I'm trying to create a template to
make sure that we can all follow this to
be able to produce a course for open AI's
team for them to be able to do a complex
course on AI though.
And they have all the necessary code
pieces to be able to
run this evasion attack.
So that's what we are doing.
And for this, for each scene, what I
provided is a screenshot, a title, a
voiceover, a scene number, and the AI
Gemini notes with the code pieces.
So the post-production can do it.
But still, as far as I understood, you
guys are not using the AI that much to be
able to create a post-production plan.
I will create a post-production plan and
with artificial intelligence, not myself.
and record it during the process how I
create the post-production plan then use
my existing footage as an input and Use
the AI's plan and then create an output a
post-production end-to-end and show the
post-production team of star weaver So
how you guys can edit one video and I
will fix the problems and I will see
Where my gaps are on the post-production
plan So you guys will be able to give me
a go ahead for one screen capture Then I
will go ahead and finish the remaining
ten screen captures in this style.
So that is where we are it
So you're trying to say that you're going
to record My I mean all the elements
separately and then you're going to both
produce that yeah And give you guys a
plan so you guys can follow up that plan
This is an advanced level course for open
AI steam the people who are using
creating the artificial intelligence This
course if just shut it will take one hour
to two hours just for one module There is
ten different tools
that comes in in here.
So I shut it in a style of 16 seconds
screen captures, but it is Overloading
the video production team because video
production team is having a hard time
then to show the audio Then to show the
video then to show an animation meant to
show the presentation For me it is clear
but for them it is not clear.
I say top right.
It's on the top left.
They are unable to Remove the right
keyword from the audio.
They need to say it's on the top I know
it, but they don't know it and I can also
relate to them as well though.
It is not that easy So I will give them
the post-production plan But what I will
do is I will go to the AI create a
post-production plan for each scene
Put it there for you.
I will edit it for you.
So you guys will see the input, the
footage that I create, the
post-production plan
that the AI has created.
And I will record how I am doing it so
you guys can do it for the other videos.
And I will show you guys the output so
the learner can learn it.
The learner meaning the open AI audience
can learn how to secure their own models.
These are highly technical people.
They also don't want a one-hour course.
They want three minute
video for one screen capture.
They will be able to
trigger most of these stuff.
Because the Starweaver is focused on
doing the video production, not on the AI
pieces, but that open AI people are
focused on the AI pieces.
When I say code spaces,
they understand code spaces.
When I say Gemini,
they understand Gemini.
And to speed this process up, I use the
AI and show the learners how I am turning
on these systems using
artificial intelligence.
So there is lots of AI support.
This is an AI course.
We are going to use the AI to be able to
plan it, to be able to produce
it, and to be able to post it.
I know it is a transformational time for
video production to use artificial
intelligence as a heads-up display.
But I will do it to you guys so you guys
will be able to learn how to do this.
And I will see where my gaps are in terms
of the post-production plan.
And Mamed and Svetyal already said this
will add one more layer on top.
But with this rise of the AI, let me tell
you guys something very important.
The old jobs are...
Bye-bye.
This is the reality.
There is going to be new jobs.
If we go back to 100 years ago, there is
lots of people that are doing the horses.
Lots of people that are cleaning the
horse shit all over the streets.
There are lots of dead horses There was a
big economy that economy is gone There is
no more video editors in the future.
There is no more coders in the future
There is all these new roles that are
coming up So we are using the AI and you
guys are not anymore video editors You
guys are AI enabled Something else not a
video editor not even a video editor Not
even the roles that you guys think so we
are entering into that kind of a future I
understand we are at that timeline and it
is creating an issue for you guys But
that is the reality and these guys who
are going to take this course are Driving
this the open AI people who are going to
take this course are driving this So it
is okay for them to get a compressed
course There I put all these ten
different tools that they are going to
use and it is creating an overload in you
guys I also understand I
call it Can you do one thing?
Sorry to interrupt you.
So if it can we do one thing?
Can you simplify this process to because
the I'll tell you You you have worked
with us and how star
we were generally works.
It's very simple We just asked the SMEs
to create some, you know demo demos using
screen shares so With audio so only that
pattern there is another type which is
which you have already done Which is just
a talking head where you are talking in
front of the camera so By any chance we
can can we simplify this so that you know
We follow the process that we
are falling from so many years
only Only your course.
I will tell you to be honest only your
course where we have to work in a
different manner Yes, because I we want
you to feel comfortable Mm-hmm
Get ready, get ready,
these horses are gonna go.
What you are telling me, I am using AI to
create this, and you are
telling me, why do we have roads?
Why do we have cars?
We have nice horses here.
Why don't we use the horses?
I feel you should work internally as our
internal star viewer team.
But you guys are trying to
use AI as well in the website.
There is lots of stuff written about AI.
Come on, use the AI.
In production also we use a lot of
artificial intelligence,
scripting and everything.
A lot of it we use it.
So I will show you guys how to use AI.
The content, SME is very relevant for us
and what it comes from, horses, that is a
very critical part and we
cannot play around with that.
The content we receive from you.
Yes, I will show how I use the AI, how to
create the post-production plan using the
existing stuff that I
have provided to you guys.
So you guys will be able to see and
create the video, not just talk.
Create the video.
I will show you guys.
This car can go from
New York to San Francisco.
And we don't need a horse to go from New
York to San Francisco.
This car goes very fast.
The AI will be able to
do the post-production.
But right now if you think that you need
a horse, you are trying to put the horse
inside the car and try to go from New
York to San Francisco.
I am not trying to do that.
I am trying to use the AI to build the
course and to make
sure we go from A to B.
I know it is not easy.
I know it is a big change.
It is a big transitional time all over
the world for everyone.
Do not forget these courses for OpenAI.
That is for the audience.
The title of the courses.
How do you secure your AI models?
These courses for them.
Yeah, so I will tell
you something, Rifat.
So what we can do is, you create your
first piece of screen shares.
According to your style,
let's share it with us.
Let's you, me and Manu connect once again
and see how things can be, you know, much
smoother following our process.
Uma, hold on.
I created 10 screen shares.
The screen shares are already created.
What the team cannot follow it is when
they are going to put the screen shares.
That is their problem.
The screen shares are already there.
The screen shares are already created.
Manu, can you share
some of his screen shares?
Look, the screen
shares are already created.
I think once you start sharing your
screen, I think you go there.
The screen shares are already created.
The images are already there.
The voiceover is there.
The screen ID is there.
They are already there.
What is not there is the plan to be able
to place them step by step is not there.
Thus, I already
created the screen shares.
They are already there and
I already read through them.
They see this.
I tell them, be mindful of
the compute costs, it says.
While we use free tiers today, training a
large scale adversarial attacks in real
worlds gets expensive fast.
There is an image there
and it shows the pricing.
And another option is and there is also
the transitional light.
So I gave you guys the images.
I gave you guys the audio.
Yes, I gave you guys.
I'm a bit too loud.
I'm in a hotel.
I hope I didn't wake up everyone.
I gave you guys the images.
I gave you guys the audio.
So, sorry, image and
where to show the video part.
So that we are facing and in some slides
we are having three images.
So in the three images we have to show it
separately or we have to show it together
like that we are having that.
So Hari, do you have this in the slide
format or what is the output?
So in Canva there is one Canva entire
podcast presentation that has embedded
videos seen by scene, every scene is
defined, every scene there are images
like so there are
three images in one video.
Now while we have the content for the
editors what is the problem here like
Difert also said that because he is the
expert we as laymen cannot understand
what comes into well.
While we have the content we do not know
how to align it with your view.
So do we have that audio
script in the notes or where?
Inside the video.
As well from Difert in the notes also but
the note is suppose a three line and when
a three line has to have the where does
it have to have the image then where does
that screen shape play comes in we need
to get that in scene.
Yes so basically I will tell you this if
Difert if you want to follow this
approach we call it Stole.
Types of the other one happen.
These slides you have rightly placed
those errors seen on this particular word
this image should have got whatever there
is a detail story word has to happen if
we have to follow this
approach having too many elements.
And also Uma we have reviewed couple of
slides I reviewed it
with Difert right here.
So the thing is like.
If we have multiple videos right these
are code snippets and the intensive right
so there are a lot of codes involved if
we just have so if that particular image
is shown then then can we turn off the
cameras maintenance
connections going down.
I think I've discussed this thing with
Rifat as well so the cognitive load is
something which we'd have to see like for
example there is a 16 second demo and we
are trying to show that corresponding to
a three or four word narration.
This is something which we'll have to
have a look into because there needs to
be enough settlement time for the learner
to kind of understand what is coming on
the screen and there needs to be proper
annotations to that point which the SME
or Rifat is actually referring to right
so this is the actual code which Rifat
was talking about so that needs to be
kind of annotated or highlighted so those
things would need to happen when we
provide a very big image or a code
snippet right so such things need to be
there otherwise it would add a lot of
cognitive load for the learner to kind of
even understand he or she would not even
able to understand what has been even
covered right so because things would
come and go on the screen.
Hanukkah this is not a course for
beginners this is for the course who is
creating the artificial intelligence they
will be able to get this much load
because as we said if I make this in one
shot this is a one hour two hour video
for just three minutes those people do
not have first of all that much of a time
and they already know when
I show them the Gemini you.
or code spaces or Jupyter Labs,
they already know what is there.
So this is an advanced level course, 16
seconds per a screen capture and a three
second for an image is enough for them.
I'm just gluing all the
parts so they can make this work.
Yeah, so there needs
to be proper annotation.
Even though it can be for an advanced
level learner, that's fine, I understand.
They might not need things to be
explained in much more detail, but the
thing is that there needs to be enough
settlement time for anyone who views the
video to kind of
actually read the things.
Not anyone, not anyone.
This is just for the open AI team.
This is not for everyone.
Everyone, I completely agree.
Everyone will not be able to get this,
such as you go and
watch a boxing training,
heavyweight boxer training, you won't be
able to go to street and the heavyweight
boxing, somebody will
beat you up, a boxer.
This is just for the heavyweight boxer.
Not for you, not for everyone.
This is not for everyone.
But still we need to
provide proper annotation.
See, the thing is when client reviews it,
they are not an expert like you are in
this particular subject.
So when they also would review, they
would understand from this perspective,
settlement time, cognitive
load and all those things.
So these are things which as
instructional designers, we
take things into consideration.
Yes, the cognitive load can be taken, by
creating animations at
the correct timeline.
The more animations that you do, the less
cognitive load the audience will have.
So you need to create such
as one side, (Audio Cuts Out)
Told you once they say running state of
the kernel, you need to
show the kernel animation.
So you take the cognitive load from the
text and put it to the animation.
Yes, you can do that.
Take the cognitive load from them by
creating animations at
the correct time line.
So I will give that on the
post-production plan to you as well.
Yeah, so these were
some of my observations.
Yes, let me do one video.
Let me do one video with the
post-production output
and the plan and the input.
Then if you see that this can be created
with a plan, with the footages, then your
questions will be solved.
Is that correct?
And I show you how I do it on DaVinci
Resolve, show all the
steps and record myself.
Will that be enough
or is this not enough?
I will give you the input, I will give
you the plan and I will give you the
output, the final output.
But Rifat, that is
going to take time, right?
So how long will that take?
I will finish this at
the end of this weekend.
I will give it to you guys.
Oh, only for the question.
Yeah.
Because I've already given all the screen
captures, all the plan, you guys are
seeing, you guys can't do it.
I understand, I empathize and I will do
it one and record the
training for you guys.
You guys will take the training and do
the post-production.
That's my thought process.
If you guys are unable to do it, somebody
says they can do it.
I will show you guys how
to do it, use the AI. I
will use the artificial intelligence,
create the post-production plan,
implement that
post-production plan, show you.
You guys that this is doable, you guys
are using the horses.
I will use the AI, the
car, to go from A to B.
Show you guys this
can be done by the car.
You guys will become less skeptic and
say, okay, a car can go from New York to
San Francisco and I don't need a horse.
I will show the car.
The car can move.
I will use the AI on the post-production
process for the planning.
So you guys will be able to say, okay,
this plan can be followed.
I can use these footages and create them.
If all of this is fine.
So the idea of using AI is to
work faster and smarter, right?
So if this is going to delay for another
two, three months is
not making sense for us.
No, no, on this project,
I never delayed the time.
You talked to my mates.
I always gave for
Sangha before everybody else.
I always waited for the Starweaver site.
You guys never ever
have waited on my site.
Zero time waited on my site.
Zero.
I always gave it to my site.
It is on your site.
And I'm also okay to create the guides,
how you guys are gonna do it.
It is on your site.
I'm okay to do that.
I have no issue doing that.
I will take my time, create the
post-production plan, do one video edit
and can, because it's
only a six minute video.
It will take my eight
hours, my one weekend.
I will be able to finish it off.
I still understand.
It will take eight hours for me to finish
this post-production because I create
YouTube videos weekly and it takes around
eight hours for me to finish all my
YouTube videos for the post-production.
I'm not saying it's an easy process, but
somebody needs to guide you.
I have already created this.
much of a guidance I can go ahead and
complete the remaining and you guys will
be able to see it and if I have any gaps
I will fix it in the processes of there
could be gaps that I have that I'm saying
there's a car use it but I'm not showing
the accelerator I'm not showing the wheel
and it might not make sense if you always
ridden a horse you have never seen a car
you have never seen a wheel it might not
make sense I will show it to you because
I'm using artificial
intelligence to be able to do it.
So let's do one thing what I will do is
I'll just go through the yeah so what we
can do is yeah just allow me one minute
so what we can do so what we can do I
think somebody's playing somebody's
playing but there's an
interruption from Arin.
Can you check your background?
Hari wants to add something yes Hari what
is it that you want to say?
No for the in that existing storyboard so
it is possible to add so that image if
you are showing means just take the audio
part so from this audio part to this one
show this image or firstly we have to
show the video means just make a number
of that for a firstly we have to show the
video means make it number one and the
next we if we have to show the image
means make it number two and just place
the audio I will do I think that will be
easy yes I will have using number code
them in each scene so you know which one
comes one two three four five and I will
put that on my post-production plan and
guide there I think that will be that
will be easy so instead of creating a new
one like I'll share my ones.
Suppose when I guess you got me screen.
Yes, I can.
When it comes to this one slide 5, so we
have this audio part.
So for this slide 5, first we have to
show the video part.
It means just to
mention this one audio part.
So from exactly which audio from which
were to which one we have to show this
video and this image is also there.
So we have to show the image this after
the video means just to mention it as a
number 2 and just to copy and paste that
audio part near to that image.
We can pick it up that one easily.
Alright, I will give you the number codes
and how it's going to get edited out on
AI generated video production plan and I
will go over that video production plan
and execute it and make sure that it is
usable and you will be able to see the
output, the numbers,
the plan and the input.
So you have everything to be able to
create one video and give me a go at but
it will take me this weekend to be able
to complete it because I'm traveling.
I'm in a hotel right now.
I will go back to Cambridge and produce
it so you will be able to see it.
And you need to do is
while I'm working on it.
Who is the Haruki?
I will
Haruki Shannon.
I will give you the I will give you the
links during the
process of how I am doing it.
So you can give me the feedback while we
are working together.
I will give the update to Haruki Shinny
or I will put this to this channel to
this chat all the steps on this chat so
everybody will be able to see what I'm
doing and how I'm going through so you
guys will be able to give feedback live.
I don't know if you guys are working in
the weekend, but I had
to do it on the weekend.
So because I'm working in IBM
At the moment I would not have the time
to do it on today till the weekend But I
will add the plans over there
Okay, okay, let's do that and a real date
for that For supporting us
For now, I know it's not easy.
It's a very transitional time.
Let's use the AI I'm using the Gemini 3
right now to be able to do this And I
will give all the steps so you guys will
be able to Trigger all the prompts that
I'm using to be able to create on your
site and use it on the other video
Productions and this is going to speed up
not only this video but every video that
the Starweaver creates
Hopefully this process.
Okay
Okay, yeah
All right, then we are
going to meet next week.
I will create the video
so put all the outputs here
Yeah, if it's a shared it is with me We
are kind of we are all from the next From
the next Monday onwards, but we'll
schedule something to look at this so
that it is Continue to you guys have a
new year's
celebration right the Christmas.
Yes Yes, all right.
Okay.
I'm a contractor.
So I'm working in Christmas
That's all right.
I will share it with you and share it
with this meeting chat Is this meeting
just going to be available or not?
I don't know but yes I will take a
screenshot of everyone that joined this
call So they will be able to
be free and come in and much.
I hope the Sangha runaway.
She's like the Rufattis Yes
Yes, I've won but she's there all right,
I will share it as much as I